[Music]
every year Canadians pay millions of
dollars out of their own pockets for
medical expenses not covered by any
government health plan and that's why
every day so many Canadians choose
Manulife health insurance to protect
themselves and their family from both
routine and unexpected medical expenses
not covered by their government health
plan
[Music]
I know government health plans don't
cover everything but do we really need
extra health insurance the truth is that
there are lots of basic routine health
expenses not covered by your government
health care plan including prescription
drugs dental care and vision care all of
these things you have to pay for
yourself and if you or someone in your
family has a serious accident or illness
there are many other expenses like
physiotherapy chiropractic care private
or semi-private hospital rooms medical
devices even home care that you may also
have to pay for yourself they can add up
quickly a FlexCare health and dental
plan helps protect you and your family
from expenses like these not covered by
your government plan in fact it starts
where your government health insurance
ends that's why it's so popular with so
many Canadians
[Music]
okay I got that but what kind of plans
are there I'm a small business owner and
don't want to pay for a lot of things I
don't need don't worry with flex care
you will never have to pay for anything
you don't want or need in fact one of
the best things about flex care is that
it's so well flexible your advisor can
help you select the perfect plan for
your life and your budget flex care
offers three types of plans the drug
plus plan covers prescription drugs the
dental plus plan covers dental expenses
and the combo plus plan covers both
prescription drugs and dental care and
all plans include valuable coverage for
things like vision care visits to the
chiropractor physiotherapist emergency
medical travel insurance plus access to
services for when you need to confirm
you have received the right diagnosis
and the right treatment you can choose
basic coverage for regular dental
check-ups and coverage for generic drugs
or enhanced coverage for major dental
work like orthodontics and coverage for
brand-name drugs plus you can add on
coverage you need like semi private and
private hospital care extra vision care
and additional emergency medical travel
insurance
[Music]
I lost my group health plan when I left
my last job to start my own business
it's their plan that's right for me
absolutely it's called the follow me
health and dental plan and it can
provide uninterrupted health and dental
coverage for you and your family when
you're employment and group benefits end
and if you apply within 60 days of
losing your group health and dental
benefits there is no medical
questionnaire to fill out
[Music]
what about cost is FlexCare affordable
and is it easy to get yes and yes
flex care is definitely affordable you
can find a plan that fits you and your
budget and you have the comfort of
knowing your rates will never increase
just because of changes in your health
plus your premiums may even be
tax-deductible and it's very easy to get
there is no medical questionnaire
required for many plans and flex care is
lifetime protection because as long as
your premiums are paid it can't be
canceled without your consent simply ask
your advisor for more details and they
can help you get the individual health
and dental protection you and your
family need plus it's easy to use when
purchasing medications simply present
your Flex care card and we take care of
the rest
and remember the sooner you get flex
care the sooner you and your family will
be protected from expenses not covered
by your government health plan
[Music]
you